Ahmad Aldali

Cluj / Romania - +40747428289 - ahmadaldali88@gmail.com - LinkedIn - Github - Website - Find me

Summary:

A Software Engineer with more than 4 years of experience, and with a strong desire to succeed. An ambitious person who tries to get more experience in my profession, eager to learn new materials and skills. An amiable, persistent and competitive character.

Professional Experience:

Front-End Developer @Yoboo Health (Belgium)

Dec 2023 - Present

- Developing the application in a flexible way to adapt into the regular changes in the flow and in a user-friendly responsive way.
- Engaging in daily meetings with the team to optimize the development process.
- Working directly with UI/UX designers and converting the designs to fast front-end web pages.
- Collaborating with testers to enhance their workflow and improving overall team efficiency.
- Providing rapid support for service desk tickets, addressing both frontend and backend issues.

Full Stack Developer @Greppy Systems (Romania)

March 2022 - Dec 2023

- Developed and maintained web services and interfaces.
- Contributed to both front-end and back-end development, enhancing overall apps functionalities.
- Created new APIs and effectively utilized AWS services to improve system performance.
- Wrote comprehensive tests, troubleshot issues, and resolved bugs to ensure software reliability.

Software Engineer @ZEOUR LTD (UK)

July 2019 - June 2022

- Developed a full System (Queue Management System) from scratch to end according to SDLC.
- Developed multiple applications within QMS, for employees, customers, managers, and admins.
- Integrated the system with an SDK keypad device, a Digital Signage System, and a Feedback System for enhanced functionality.
- Developed a Self-Service Kiosk capable of accepting cash from users.
- Led a team of six members, driving project success through effective leadership and collaboration.

Skills:

Web Skills	PHP - Laravel - JavaScript - Typescript - Svelte - VueJS - HTML/CSS - RESTful APIs - Python - Django - Houdini - GraphQL - DB Management - MySQL - MongoDB - TailwindCSS
Digital Skills	JAVA - Dart - Flutter - Chrome Extensions - OOP - Design Patterns - Agile - Git - Jira - Linux - AWS - Apache - Nginx - Backend - Frontend - Figma
Soft Skills	Problem solving - Googling - Fast Learner - Work Under Pressure - Collaboration - Communication - Leadership - Helping Others - Time Management - Support Services - Attention to details

Main Projects:

Yoboo Dec 2023 - Present

- Successfully replaced the team leader role in the FE side, ensuring project stability and zero downtime during the transition.
- Collaborated with over 40 B2P and B2B partners during my first year.
- Continuously optimizing performance, leading to significant improvements in application speed and responsiveness.

Allmyfaves March 2022 - Sep 2023

- Achieved a remarkable reduction in homepage response time from 4.5 seconds to approximately 1 second, significantly enhancing user experience.
- Executed a successful migration of a legacy database (~10 GB, serving 500K users), ensuring data integrity and system reliability.
- Seamlessly transitioned to a new system version, migrating data, users, domains, and branding elements without service interruption.

Sumeet Pro July 2022 - March 2023

- Developed a Chrome extension that effectively transcribes and summarizes Google meetings.
- Created essential APIs for the extension, including dashboard functionalities and payment integrations, streamlining operations.
- Successfully deployed projects on Nginx web servers, ensuring robust performance and reliability.

Queue Management System

July 2019 - June 2022

- Attracted over 25 clients in the first year of operation, establishing a strong market presence.
- Innovated the first Telegram bot for the Queue Management System, enabling ticketing and appointment bookings through a popular messaging platform.
- Developed eight interconnected applications as microservices with flexibility for standalone or centralized operation, enhancing system adaptability.

Education

Master of Software Engineering and Information Systems.	2019 – 2021 (In-completed)
Bachelor of Informatics Engineering.	2013 – 2018 (89.08% / 3rd place)

References

1. Ioana Hazsda - Team Lead Manager @Greppy Systems

ihazsda@gmail.com (+40746990262)

2. Hassan Zaitouna - General Manager @ZEOUR LTD

hassan@zeour.co.uk (+44736052876)